A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asia Society records
1956-1999
1966-1987
Rockefeller Archive Center
Asia Society
FA110
500 Cubic Feet
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Collection was deposited at RAC by Asia Society, December 1977.
Records received by RAC in multiple accessions from 1977-2000, including, but not necessarily limited to, Accessions 1977:021, 1979:039, 1979:041, 1980:022, 1981:022, 1981:022, 1981:031, 1982:097, 1987:051, 1987:159, 1988:014, 1988:039, 1988:043, 1989:039, 1989:080, 1989:118, 1990:021, 1990:022, 1990:023, 1990:108, 1993:021, 1994:016, 1996:033, 1996:085 and 2000:022.
Biographical / Historical
The Asia Society was founded in 1956 by John D. Rockefeller 3rd to promote greater knowledge and understanding of Asia in the United States, and to strengthen the relationship between Americans and Asians through international cultural exchange. The Asia Society has grown to become a global institution with an educational mandate and cross-disciplinary programming.
The Asia Society headquarters are located in New York, and the Society maintains additional U.S. offices in California (Los Angeles and San Francisco), Texas (Houston) and Washington, D.C. and global centers in Australia (Melbourne), China (Shanghai), Hong Kong, India (Mumbai), South Korea (Seoul), and the Philippines (Manila).
Scope and Contents
All records in the collection have been received from the Asia Society New York office, and document the activities of the Society through the New York office from inception in 1956 though the 1990s. Records documenting the activities of regional offices including those in Houston, Los Angeles and Washington, D.C. are minimal.
Records include: Correspondence, reports, administrative records, meetings, studies and seminar files, officer's files, department and program records, development and fundraising files.
The early activities of the Society are particularly well documented including the Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG) and Country Council records including but not limited to those of the China Council and and the India Council.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Series 1: Public Affairs, Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG)
Subseries 1: Seminar Files
Subseries 2: Authors Files
Subseries 3: SEADAG Grant Files
Subseries 4: SEADAG Grant Reports
Subseries 5: Executive Committee Files
Subseries 6: SEADAG Country Reports
Subseries 7: SEADAG Financial Files (Non-Grant) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Subseries 8: SEADAG Financial Files (Seminars) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Subseries 9: SEADAG Financial Files (Grants) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Subseries 10: SEADAG Financial Files (Personnel) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Subseries 11: SEADAG Audio Tapes
Series 2: Country Councils
Subseries 1: Country Councils – General
Subseries 2: China Council Files
Subseries 3: India Council Files
Subseries 4: Mary Ann Siegfried (MAS) Files
Series 3: Exhibitions and Events
Subseries 1: Gallery Files
Subseries 2: Art Photos
Subseries 3: Exhibition, Publicity and Events Miscellaneous
Subseries 4: Cultural Programs
Series 4: Contemporary Affairs
Subseries 1: Forestry, Small Scale Enterprise and Publishing
Subseries 2: ECA Division
Subseries 3: Contemporary Affairs Day Files
Subseries 4: Discover Asia Files
Subseries 5: China Briefing
Subseries 6: India Briefing
Subseries 7: Philippines Files
Subseries 8: John Bresnan Chronological File
Subseries 9: Asia Society Fletcher School (Tufts University) Files
Subseries 10: Philippine President Corazon Aquino Visit
Subseries 11: Media Files
Subseries 12: Vietnam Conference
Subseries 13: Islam Files
Subseries 14: Conference Tapes and Special Formats
Series 5: Education Department, Director, Betty M. Bullard Files
Subseries 1: President's Commission on Foreign Language and International Studies Files
Subseries 2: CEMREL
Subseries 3: General Files
Subseries 4: United States-Japan Conference for Cultural and Educational Interchange (CULCON)
Subseries 5: Education Department – Textbook Evaluation Project
Subseries 6: Education Department – Videos
Series 6: Performing Arts Department, Director, Beate Gordon Files
Subseries 1: Artists and Events Files
Subseries 2: Mailing Lists
Subseries 3: Background, Publicity and Local Programs
Subseries 4: General Correspondence
Subseries 5: General Files
Subseries 6: Performing Arts Program Financial Ledgers – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Series 7: Asia Society President, Robert B. Oxnam Files
Subseries 1: Departmental Files
Subseries 2: Chronological File
Series 8: Public Affairs
Subseries 1: Asian Development Seminar Program (ADSP) – General Files
Subseries 2: Director of Public Affairs, Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) Files
Subseries 3: Public Affairs Day File
Subseries 4: ADSP – Authors, Institutions and Audio Tapes.
Subseries 5: ADSP – Seminar Reports and Background papers
Subseries 6: ADSP – Ethical Dilemmas of Development in Asia
Subseries 7: Inaugural papers
Subseries 8: Worker Migration Studies
Series 9: Publications
Subseries 1: General Files
Subseries 2: Special Formats
Subseries 3: Press Clippings
Subseries 4: Publications
Subseries 5: Publications - Asia Magazine Correspondence
Series 10: Director of Education and Communications, Timothy Plummer Files
Series 11: Administration
Subseries 1: General
Subseries 2: Corporate Programs
Subseries 3: Executive Department Files
Subseries 4: Director of Public Affairs, Marshall M. Bouton (MMB) Files
Subseries 5: Asia Society Executive Vice President, Lionel Landry Files
Subseries 6: Asia Society President, Phillips Talbot papers
Subseries 7: Director, Meetings and Studies Program, Herbert D. Spivack Files
Subseries 8: Asia Society Board of Trustees
Series 12: Programs and Programs in Association
Subseries 1: General Files
Subseries 2: Williamsburg Conferences
Subseries 3: India Council
Subseries 4: Asian Literature Program Files
Subseries 5: Tour Program Files
Subseries 6: American Committee for Borobudur, Inc. Files
Series 13: Development
Subseries 1: Special Events
Subseries 2: General Files
Subseries 3: Capital Campaign
Subseries 4: Asian Era Campaign
Subseries 5: Foundations
Series 14: Security – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
Series 15: Special Formats – General
Subseries 1: Audio (Currently closed for digitization.)
Subseries 2: Oversized
Subseries 3: Moving Images (Some portions currently closed for digitization.)
- Public Affairs, Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG), 1961-1980; 1
  Arrangement
  Series 1: Public Affairs, Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group (SEADAG)
  Subseries 1: Seminar Files
  Subseries 2: Authors Files
  Subseries 3: SEADAG Grant Files
  Subseries 4: SEADAG Grant Reports
  Subseries 5: Executive Committee Files
  Subseries 6: SEADAG Country Reports
  Subseries 7: SEADAG Financial Files (Non-Grant) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
  Subseries 8: SEADAG Financial Files (Seminars) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
  Subseries 9: SEADAG Financial Files (Grants) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
  Subseries 10: SEADAG Financial Files (Personnel) – RESTRICTED from scholarly access.
  Subseries 11: SEADAG Audio Tapes Subseries 12: SEADAG Video Recordings
  Related Materials
  See also: Series 2 and Series 8.
  Scope and Contents
  Primarily contains SEADAG records, with some materials pertaining to the Asian Development Seminar Program (ADSP) amd other Public Affairs files.
  - Seminar Files, 1
    - World Wide Private holders, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - The Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference, 1965 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference, 1965 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Johnson Foundation - Wingspread Conference, 1965 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rural Development Seminar, 1970 June 26-27 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - SEADAG, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - SEADAG, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - SEADAG, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - SEADAG Conference Papers - Honolulu, 1968 January (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - SEADAG, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SEADAG, 1968 March-May (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Research Grant Program - Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Vietnam Panel Seminar - Papers, 1971 May 7-8 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Vietnam Panel Seminar - Papers, 1971 May 7-8 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Radio - Wingspread Conference, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Subbulakshmi Concert, 1966 November 13 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Post Concert Party for Ravi Shankar, 11:00 pm, 1966 December 21 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - The Johnson Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - SEADAG Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - SEADAG Meetings, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - SEADAG Papers - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - SEADAG Library Reports, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Wingspread Conference, 1965 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Wingspread Conference, 1965 September 17 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Wingspread Conference - Kenneth T. Young Notes, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Wingspread Conference, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - SEADAG, Discussion papers, 1969 June 24-27 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - SEADAG - "Evaluation of the Southeast Asia Development Advisory Group", 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - SEADAG, Directory, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - SEADAG papers - 70: Breese, Ed.: Research Priorities for urban roles (report and papers), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-1: Parker: Administrative development in Papua and New Guinea, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-2: Lee: Agricultural Diversification and development, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-3: Lawas: Agricultural Diversification and development: Philippine viewpoint, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-4: Turley: Democratic Republic of Vietnam since Death of Ho Chi Minh?, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-5: Brown: Impact of Indochina involvement on American Political institutes, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-6: Lasswell: Implications of technological change for southeast asia?, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - SEADAG papers - 71-7:Braibanti: Policy sciences and a general theory of political change, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-1: Ou: Status of crop protection activities and crop protection problems, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-2: Montgomery: Behavioral Dimensions of technological change, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-3: Chang: Comparative analysis of non-formal ed. In SE asian ministers of ed. Org (SEAMEO) members countries, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-4: Paulston: Planning in non-formal ed. Alternatives: nat'l youth service orgs in less dev. Countries, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-5: Kitamura: Regional cooperation as seen from ECAFE, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-6: Hansen: Indonesia's green revolution: Aboandonment of non-market strategy?, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-7: Tan Jake Hooi: Urbanization planning and national development planning in Singapore, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-8: Laquian: Need for national urban strategy in the Philippines, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-9: Bruner: Expression of ethnicity in Indonesia, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-10: Brewer: A policy approach to the study of political development and change, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-11: Malmgren: Regional Cooperation Why is it necessary?, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-12: Meyer: Theories of the affects of education on civic participation, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-13: Keeny: Organizing national family planning programs; some current problems in Asia, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-14: Jones: Implications of prospective urbanization for development, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-15: Anderson: Social Strategies in population change: village data, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-16: Milone: transformation patterns in coastal metropolises of asia, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-17: Meier: Asian Innovations for developing great cities, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-18: Migsena: nutrition, health, status and impact of development on lower mekong basin, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-19: Lerner: Communication for development. In southeast asia, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - SEADAG papers - 72-20: Calavan: Cultural, environmental and socioeconomic factors in food use?, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-1: Wells: Economic Man and engineering man; choice of technology?, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-2: Fei Rains: A model of growth and employment in the open dualistic economy, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-3: Grossman et al: nutrition and some related diseases, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-4: Rambo and Jamieson: Cultural change in rural vietnam, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-5: Gable Springer: Comparing Admin. "Reality Worlds", 1973 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-6: Moos: Conceptualizing educational environments, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-7: Oshima: A labor intensive strategy for southeast asia priorities, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-8: Davies: An essay on employment concepts: The definition of labor, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-9: Nielson Kirk: Learning environments and learning outcomes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-10: Alonzo: Short-term employment creation projects in the Philippines, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-11: Labys and Weaver: towards a commodity oriented development model, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - SEADAG papers - 73-12: Wilder: Effects of literacy skills obtained through non-formal, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-1: Goodman and Franks: Between war and peace: A profile of migrants?, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-2: Encarnacion: An economic demographic model of the Philippines, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-3: Eilenstein et al: three essays on the methodological aspects, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-4: Allen: Policies of ASEAN countries towards direct foreign?, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-5: Chee: Rural Development and development administration in Malaysia, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-6: Reuber: Some aspects of private direct investment in developing countries, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-7: Raksasataya: Foreign aid and the choice of technique of road?, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-8: McCleary: Foreign aid to public administrations in Thailand in 1980's, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-9: Panitchpakdi: Human Resource development and foreign aid:?, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-10: Hughes: Distribution of gains from foreign direct investment?, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-11: Chen: The "Planned birth" program of the PRC, with breif analysis, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - SEADAG papers - 74-12: Lee: Legal aspects of implementing a total national population program, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - SEADAG papers - 75-1: Scott: Exploitation in rural class relations: A victim's perspective, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - SEADAG papers - 75-2: Elliot: Political integration in North Vietnam: The cooperativization period, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - SEADAG papers - 75-3: Medina: Philippine experience with land reform since 1972:.., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - SEADAG papers - 75-4: Birowo: BIMAS: a package program for intensification?, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - SEADAG papers - 75-5: Harkin: Strengths and weakness of the Philippines land reform, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - SEADAG papers - 76-1: Ingersoll et al: Resettlement and settlement: annotated biblio., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - SEADAG papers - 76-2: Montgomery: Food for thought: 3 recipes for appraising nutrition, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - SEADAG reports - Rural: Research needs in Ag. Diversification, Manila, 1971 January (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Rural-urban linkage, Wahington D.C., 1971 February (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: Non-economic factors in Indonesian Development, Elkridge, 1971 February (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - SEADAG reports - Vietnam: The Future of Indochina: A political assessment, NYC, 1971 May (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - SEADAG reports - ED/Human: New Strategies for Educational Development, Washington, D.C., 1971 May (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - SEADAG reports - Mekong: Mekong resettlement, Washington D.C., 1971 May (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - SEADAG reports - Urban: Urbanization Policy and national development, Ithaca, NY, 1971 July (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - SEADAG reports - Dev/Admin: Administrative processes: Value Reformation, Durham, NC, 1971 August (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - SEADAG reports - Rural: Application of 'systems Analysis in research, San Francisco, CA, 1971 September (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - SEADAG reports - Urban: fiscal Policy for housing Urban development, Madison, WI, 1971 October (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - SEADAG reports - Rural: Research needs on crop protection systems, Bangkok, Thailand, 1971 November (Box 9, Folder 100)
    - SEADAG reports - Dev/Admin: Administrative processes: Value Reformation, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia, 1971 November (Box 9, Folder 101)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: Relation of local level inputs, Chapel Hill, NC, 1971 December (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - SEADAG reports - Vietnam: Role of election in vietnamese political development, NYC, 1971 December (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - SEADAG reports - Regional: Non-economic aspects of regional cooperation, NYC, 1971 December (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - SEADAG reports - Urban: Urbanization and national development planning, Manila, 1972 January (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - SEADAG reports - Regional: Trade and monetary cooperation in southeast asia, Bangkok, Thailand, 1973 January (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - SEADAG reports - Mekong: The impact of development on the fisheries, Santa Barbara, CA, 1972 February (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - SEADAG reports - Dev/Admin: Value assumption in the development process, Singapore, 1972 March (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: The relation of local level inputs, NYC, 1972 March (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - SEADAG reports - Population - Population growth and development in southeast asia, Elkridge, 1972 April (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - SEADAG reports - ED/Human: Ed. For civic and communal participation, Santa Fe, NM, 1972 May (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Problems of organizational control and coordination, Washington D.C., 1972 June (Box 9, Folder 112)
    - SEADAG reports - Population: Pop. Change and development in southeast asia, Pattaya, 1972 June (Box 9, Folder 113)
    - SEADAG reports - Population: Pop. Growth and development in Southeast Asia, San Francisco, CA, 1972 July (Box 9, Folder 114)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Urban Future in southeast asia, Berkeley, CA, 1972 August (Box 9, Folder 115)
    - SEADAG reports - Regional: Exchange Rates as a problem of Southeast Asia Region, Singapore, 1972 August (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - SEADAG reports - Mekong: Nutrition and public health in Mekong development planning, NYC, 1972 August (Box 10, Folder 117)
    - SEADAG reports - Rural: Commodity approach to sectoral planning for rural development, Singapore, 1972 September (Box 10, Folder 118)
    - SEADAG reports - ED/Human: Individual Modernization: Socialization, Chieng Mai, 1972 November (Box 10, Folder 119)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Employment Creation Strategies for SE Asian Economies, Atlanta, GA, 1972 December (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - SEADAG reports - Summary: Urbanization and national development in Southeast Asia (Dotson), 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - SEADAG reports - Summary: Population growth and development in Southeast Asia (Taueber), 1972 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - SEADAG reports - Dev/Admin: Factors of administrative productivity, NYC, 1973 March (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: SE Asian Development goals, 1980, NYC, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: foreign Capital investment problems in Indonesia, Medan, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - SEADAG reports - Mekong: Strategies for nutrition intervention in Mekong, Singapore, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 126)
    - SEADAG reports - ED/Human: Ed. Institutions as social environments, Aspen, CO, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - SEADAG reports - Rural: Directions in rural development planning, NYC, 1973 July (Box 10, Folder 128)
    - SEADAG reports - DEV/Admin: Administrative Requirements for labor intensive, Singapore, 1973 July (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Short-Term employment creation projects in SE Asia, Baguio, 1973 August (Box 10, Folder 130)
    - SEADAG reports - ED/Human: Ed. And national development, Singapore, 1973 September (Box 11, Folder 131)
    - SEADAG reports - Urban: Urban and regional planning: The State of the art, Savannah, GA, 1973 October (Box 11, Folder 132)
    - SEADAG reports - Population: Role of population planning in Gen. Economic Planning, San Francisco, CA, 1973 November (Box 11, Folder 133)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: The Multinational firm in Southeast Asia, La Jolla, CA, 1973 December (Box 11, Folder 134)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: Problems for social development. Planning in Indonesia, Ujung Pandang, 1974 January (Box 11, Folder 135)
    - SEADAG reports - Vietnam: Impact of western presence upon Vietnamese, NYC, 1974 January (Box 11, Folder 136)
    - SEADAG reports - MEKONG: Regional Development as it concerns specialization, Ithaca, NY, 1974 March (Box 11, Folder 137)
    - SEADAG reports - Dev/Admin: Rural local government and Dev. Administration in Southeast Asia, Ithaca, NY, 1974 April (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - SEADAG reports - Urban: Urban and regional planning: Southeast Asia experience, Bali, 1974 April (Box 11, Folder 139)
    - SEADAG reports - rural: peasants, land reform, and Revolutionary movements, Savannah, GA, 1974 June (Box 11, Folder 140)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Role of foreign aid to Thailand in the 1980's, Chieng Mai, 1974 June (Box 11, Folder 141)
    - SEADAG reports - Population: Implementing a total National program for fertility, Bali, 1974 August (Box 11, Folder 142)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Multinational corporations in Southeast Asia, Penang, 1974 June (Box 11, Folder 143)
    - SEADAG reports - ADHOC: Communist Movements and Regimes in Indochina, NYC, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - SEADAG reports - MEKONG: Interaction of Planning and Implementation for Rural, Pattaya, 1974 August (Box 11, Folder 145)
    - SEADAG reports - Indonesia: Planning for regional development, Bukittinggi, 1974 September (Box 11, Folder 146)